All of the events that happened after Fushi went into his deep slumber in Renril.
Bon told to Fushi.
Please don't die and leave me behind.
Everyone was so very kind.
Right to the end.
To Takunaha?
What brought this on? How'd you manage to get it?
Fushi said goodbye as Gugu left for Takunaha.
How did you come to?
Love a sleep life.
F Hari!
In Namely Tanaka.
Thank you.
Excellent. Go get them.
Welcome to all of our new first graders.
Congratulations on your very first day at Minamoto Elementary School.
Hello there.
Nice to meet you. I'm March. Why don't we be friends?
Your name is March? March is a weird name.
It's nice to meet you too. I'm March. Why don't we all be friends?
What's that thing you have on the top of your head?
Let me see. Isn't it cute?
My mommy made it for me.
Don't you know that you're really not supposed to bring anything like this into school?
It's not allowed. My mommy told me.
Well, why not? You have something in your hair as well.
Mine are allowed, but yours is just a silly decoration.
That's not fair! You have decorations!
I've always had these ribbons in my hair, so they don't really count.
Well, I've always had this on my head as well, so damn!
Oh, yeah? How long?
For 500 years!
500 years!
Liar!
I'm not lying, teacher! One of the new students in the school is a crazy fat liar!
I really hope March is doing okay. She'll be fine. She's very sociable, and Bond's there too.
Hey, Aiko, you'll need the first year's entrance. It's over there.
Thanks. See you later.
Go knock him out!
Oh, yeah!
Hey, everyone.
President! Good morning to you!
Oh, hey, Fushi. You're close to Mizuha, right?
It's just that we've been looking for her name, but we can't find her on any of the class lists.
Huh?
She transferred to another school. Something to do with her father's work, I think.
How come we didn't hear anything about this before?
Well, it was pretty sudden.
Hana, you really didn't know about this?
I had no idea. Sorry.
Right. You don't wear your hair accessory anymore, so I thought something might have happened.
How'd it go?
Looks like they're not in. Do you think they've already moved out of town?
I think they're just ignoring us.
Why do you think that?
I've been checking in on Mizuha's place for a while. I've never seen them moving out.
Oh, good. That means...
It's Mizuha's birthday tomorrow, isn't it?
I want to see her smile again, even if it's just one more time!
I would do anything to make that happen! Anything!
Me too. I wonder what it would take to make her smile again.
Right. Now smile!
Smile!
Hello there, Marge. Did you have fun?
Oh, dear. What's the matter? Is it something that happened at school today?
Oh, hi, Bun.
Why, hello, Mimory. Look, Marge. It's Mimory. Did you know she goes to your school, too?
Oh, Marge. Right. She's the one who Fushi was talking about. His mom?
Huh? What did you say?
Nothing. Is she okay?
Well, I think she's feeling pretty fed up with school right now.
That's just like me. It's true.
Oh, Fushi.
What's Marge doing over there?
Oh, she's just making mud balls with Mimory. Is something the matter, Fushi?
Gugu sent me a message. He wants to see Marge dressed up for school.
Good timing. She was crying until just now.
She was?
I'm afraid she doesn't like school, but now she's finally smiling.
Great, but how come?
Well, just watch.
Oh, right. The attention grabbed no jutsu.
Something that remained after Mimory left.
Something that makes a connection between people.
Something that makes a connection across time.
Something that brings smiles.
It's Mizuha's birthday tomorrow, isn't it?
Oh.
Maybe I should send her a gift.
Happy birthday to me.
Happy birthday, dear Mimory.
Mizuha.
Izumi's PC is supposed to have some sort of records of Mizuha in there somewhere.
We can print the photos out and give them to her as a gift.
That's a really nice idea, Fushi.
The password is 0406.
There.
At the very least, I want her to know the truth.
That all her mother wanted was to remember her exactly the way she was.
She didn't want to forget all those memories.
I bet.
Okay, it's all done.
They're all taped inside the book.
What are you all doing?
Check it out.
We made a really cool birthday gift for Mizuha.
A special photo album.
I want to make it even cuter.
I got a bunch of new stickers yesterday.
Wow, looks great.
There.
Huh?
How come you were in that shed?
What were you doing in there, Fushi?
Nothing.
Why do you guys look so gloomy?
Is something wrong?
We were just updating them about what happened up until now.
So we were just discussing whether we should do something about Mizuha disappearing.
But unfortunately, we don't know what we can do.
I don't think you need to worry too much about it, Hana.
Something happened between you and Mizuha, though.
Is that right?
I think it's more important to know what she's doing than where she is right now.
So, does that mean you do know?
You know what Mizuha's up to, Fushi?
No.
If only there was a way that we could get her to see that she has people around her who really do care about her.
Although, I'm not entirely sure what we would say to her even if we did see her.
And if we said the wrong thing to her, then we might lose her forever.
Well, in that case, let's keep it simple.
And the best way is to ask this question.
Hana, do you want to see Mizuha again?
Yeah, I really do.
I miss her.
There's a chance that she might not let us in, but let's at least try and drop by her place anyway.
Yeah, good idea. I made her this new birthday gift as well.
Was it you who dropped this in our mailbox?
You must be your dad!
It's a special birthday gift for Mizuha!
Well, I'm sorry, but I'm sure she'll refuse it.
My daughter has already moved on.
She's cut off her past.
We do not intend to return.
But where are you guys moving to?
Somewhere you can never come or visit.
I'm leaving with my daughter first thing tomorrow.
And we're going so far that you won't be able to be friends anymore.
I hope that you all understand.
Well, it looks like there's no point in going.
That was nice of him to go out of his way to bring it back to us.
It was.
No, this fell out.
I thought we taped everything in.
Huh?
I don't remember this photo.
My beloved family.
What is this?
We should still go check out Mizuha's new place.
I think we should give up on that.
We'd just be causing more trouble for her.
Crap!
I still haven't confessed to Mizuha how I feel!
I have to do it!
So I'm coming with!
It's my last chance!
Well then, you have to tell her how you feel, Yuki!
I know, right?
Let's do it, Vice President!
We all stand behind you.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Our guest today is the Renro weed removal expert, Harumaki,
of the Tasty Peach Foundation.
Hello!
Bond's on the TV again.
This one's live broadcast.
He's famous now!
Would you mind telling Bond to stop skipping his work at school?
He hasn't been there in ages, and the principal is really furious with him.
See you later!
Hey, Tanari, wait up!
Huh?
Could you do me a favor?
I left my school body in the custodian's room.
Do you mind checking to see if it's still hidden?
But why me?
I'm skipping school today.
I'm telling Mizuha how I feel about her today!
It's my very last chance!
And I'm going to help him.
Huh?
You get it?
It's an important day.
Let's go!
But I don't get it!
Welcome back, Fushi!
How'd it go?
They live near her grandfather's house now.
Underground, probably.
I think it's connected to that place where Fenn and Nixon went.
All right, so we're stepping into the enemy stronghold!
The Occult Research Club!
Let's go!
ORC, fight!
It's not the ORC or the Handicrafts Club.
This isn't even a club event.
Hold on!
You're all coming?
That was the agreement, after all.
Of course we're all coming!
Vice Principal Yuki's romantic life is on the line!
You're coming with us as well, aren't you, Hana?
Uh, yeah.
Well, this will be my first time skipping school.
All right, then.
But the second it gets dangerous, we're turning back, okay?
Roger that!
Sir!
Hey, I'm the leader of the Occult Research Club!
It's pretty far, isn't it?
Guess we'll take the bus.
Come on, guys!
I said I'm the leader!
Oh, and by the way, when you take the detergent back, do you mind taking this gas canister as well?
What a giant pain in the butt.
You didn't hide your body well at all!
Oh, man.
You still need me to help you.
Huh?
Hey, I used to use this bow.
Man, what a throwback!
Wait, why do you have these weapons here?
Come to think of it, what are you up to anyway, Fushi?
We're here.
Maybe we should go and say hello to her grandpa?
We shouldn't say hi to the enemy.
Wait, he's an enemy?
Enemy?
I like the sound of that!
Her grandpa?
I don't understand.
Ugh!
Do we really need to enter through here?
The tunnel's closed tight with a steel door.
I could break it open, but that would take too long.
It's the entrance to a city of mazes!
Mizuha's really beyond these tunnels?
That's unreal.
Looks like it's time for the brains of this unit.
Send us Suzuhiko to shine!
I'll use the map on my laptop.
There's no internet down here!
That way.
The one on the right.
Be careful and try not to slip.
How did you know it's this one?
Fushi has this cool way of connecting to the roots through the tunnels.
So that means you can sense which is the right way.
So you know what's ahead of us then?
As long as it's somewhere the roots can reach, that means, wherever the roots can't reach, it's safe to say that's where the enemy will be.
A steel door, huh?
This looks like a job for the muscle of the team.
Ow!
My arm!
Are you okay, Kazuma?
Yay!
It's open!
Nice one, Fushi!
Thanks to Nando.
It looks like a total maze from here on out.
And every route leads to a steel door.
We won't know what's ahead until we open them.
Looks like it's my time to shine!
I brought just the thing to show us the way!
Ta-da!
Presenting the Ouija board!
We can use this to ask the spirits!
The spirits?
Oh.
Ghosts?
Spirits?
Anyone at all?
Hear my call and tell us the way to Mizuha!
Thank you very much!
They're always playing with those things.
It's silly.
It moved!
Arr!
Wait, are you kidding me?
Right!
We go right!
It's this way!
Let's go!
Thanks, you guys!
We go!
We go right now!
An area closed off behind steel.
Isn't this the place Ven and Nixon mentioned?
Sure looks like it.
Mizuha's through there.
This is far enough.
You guys need to head back.
But we came all this way.
I wish you could have seen Mizuha.
I really do.
But if that's the only way in, it's too dangerous.
I don't think the knockers would let you through.
Ew, that's the enemy.
A knocker and the weird flesh.
Super nasty.
Be careful, Fushi.
Have a backup body ready just in case.
Yeah, and you take care of the others.
I will.
Good luck.
Greetings and salutations to you, Fushi.
Come on in.
Please, do help yourself.
Look, Mizuha.
Fushi has come all this way to see you.
Your birthday gift.
It's delayed, but I wanted to deliver it to you.
Oh my, it's an album.
Well, wanna look?
No, you don't?
I'm so sorry.
She's been acting so selfish lately.
Well, what do you want, Mizuha?
Hmm, what's that?
You want Fushi?
Whatever shall I do with you?
There is no real Fushi, Mizuha.
You see, what's in front of you is the body of a person I once met long ago.
Is that really what you want?
You're real.
You're here in front of me, and you're even talking to me.
Hey, knocker.
You're the one keeping Mizuha here, aren't you?
The outside world is painful to Mizuha.
Until it finally becomes a paradise, Mizuha's mind and soul will both need to remain here.
Mizuha, is that what you honestly want?
You really believe?
What's your true wish?
I know that everyone wants you to come back.
Me too.
Alright.
So then tell me, if I were to die, would you cry for me?
Yeah.
You liar.
You know full well that you've never cried before.
Yes, I have.
You mean the time you became a sea turtle?
They don't count as human tears.
I can't trust you.
I'm afraid nothing you say rings true to me.
How can I ever believe a word you say?
I mean, you're always prepared to run away at a moment's notice.
Mizuha, do you know I envy you?
You've been Mizuha since the day you were born, and you've always been allowed to be Mizuha.
Yes, but only as my mother's trophy.
That's not true.
Izumi tried to raise you as a person that she could be proud of, and maybe that upset you.
But she... she honestly loved you.
That much is certain.
Liar.
You're full of shit.
You can't even prove it to me.
I can, with that photo album.
Take a look, and it'll prove your mom loves you.
The knocker caused amnesia for Izumi.
Those painful memories.
You were always involved in them.
But she never wanted to forget those days she spent with you.
She held on to them.
I remember this.
All of it.
I remember.
What are you doing showing me these photos, Fushi?
These are painful memories.
You really shouldn't have looked at this photo album.
Now then, it's about time we got started.
Hey, stop that!
Let me go!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Mizuha.
Um, so, I know this might be rude to say in front of your family,
but I really don't think you belong here, Mizuha.
I really want you to come back.
Why'd you come here, especially when I know you don't even care about me?
Don't care.
Why would you ever say something like that?
We are just full of empty words.
Doesn't it mean anything that we came all this way?
We worked together to find you because all of us care a lot about you!
Please stop shouting at me, Hana.
It's annoying.
Don't change the subject.
Why do you need to be down here?
May I ask a question?
Mizuha, are you seeing a doctor?
No, why?
Well, pretend I'm a doctor and hear me out.
The insufficient exposure to sunlight is bad for your health and could put you at risk for osteoporosis.
Well, you're not a doctor, so I'm not listening to you.
Copy that!
Mizuha, I have no idea what your life was like growing up.
And it might be impossible for me to give you what you need,
but I want to do whatever I can to help you.
You don't need to do anything anymore, Hana.
Yeah, I don't expect a single thing from you.
But then, now what am I supposed to do?
Um, pardon me, but it really smells of stagnant water down here.
Huh?
And furthermore, I have to add, that cake looks absolutely disgusting.
I recommend you leave before you stink.
Who here agrees with me?
Hmm.
You're all awful, people!
How could you be so rude?
She ought to kick you out of here right now!
Right now?
I don't really think that's a good idea.
Uh, why?
Your dream is to make everyone else's dream come true, right, Fushi?
So for that to fully happen, the world has to be peaceful.
And you see, I have figured out what peace is.
Thank you.
Okay.
We'll be right back.